For buying in ICICI Loards futures, the
stop loss will be 1915. 1972,
1985 and 2000 are the targets.
I want to tell you honestly that
I have given these targets very small. Okay, yes,
I think if any stock can
try to surprise today, then it should be
ICICI.
After the excellent results of the real insurance company, the numbers of this general insurance company are also
coming very good. The results are
much better than expected. The
growth in motor insurance premium is
commendable. I think this stock will also be
in the mood to do something good today. Okay, for
selling in RBL Bank futures,
check if RBL is not under the ban. If it is under the
ban, then do
one thing. Remove the futures.
Write bank cash in the empty RBL. Only those who have it should sell. They will
not be able to sell in futures. You should take cash. The
stop loss will be 158. Your
target is 148, 144 and 140. These are the three targets.
Today there can be an accident. It is not a big deal.
If you decide to buy it, then  How much should it
fall? 4 pa will do. If it opens at 7, 8
or if it opens directly at 10 then the work will be over.
This is to be decided. But today
's accident is clear cut RBL. There is
no doubt in it on every parameter,
meaning, look at the front, back, up, down, right, left, I mean,
look at the numbers are very bad. There are big right-
offs. Credit cost is increasing. There is no
relief anywhere. I don't know what is happening.
People have been very disappointed in this bank. Kotak
Bank result is better than expected. It is better than other
banks. The updates came out.
After looking at the numbers of banks and exchanges, Kotak is looking good. After that, it is
not looking that good on its own.
But if you look at others, it
looks better. Yes, sometimes a
person is
not very good himself,
but with whom you are looking, it makes a lot of
difference. This is the thing with Kotak. So,
deposit growth is very good. It is a
difficult environment for banks right now,
but the company has given a healthy performance in it. There is
no problem in this.
Look for buying opportunities on the sidelines. Support at 1750 is
not too far away. It will
start weakening below that. One should not go with my advice. On the
upside, it can travel up to 1800-1810.
Kotak Bank